JOHN BRINK

STUDENT IN INTERACTIVE MEDIA TECHNOLOGY



C O N T A C T I N F O R M A T I O N

+46 70 65 250 88

<u>john-brink@hotmail.com</u>

https://johnbrink.netlify.app

in John Brink

johnbri

COMPETENCES

UX Research	••••	Javascript	••••
UI Prototyping	••••	React.js	••••
Figma	••••	Wordpress	••••
Adobe CC	••••	Python	••••
CSS	••••	Java	••••
HTML	••••	C#	••••

LANGUAGES

Swedish
English
French

PROFILE

As a student in interactive media technology, I have developed skills for researching, creating, and evaluating digital products with a focus on human-computer interaction. My current goals are to build my knowledge in web development and UX design to a professional level. People often describe me as creative, open-minded, down-to-earth, responsible, calm, just to name a few.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

M.Sc. in Engineering - Interactive Media Technology KTH ROYAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, STOCKHOLM AUG 2018 - PRESENT (GRADUATING JUN 2023)

Summer course - Web Management

LINNAEUS UNIVERSITY, VÄXJÖ JUNE 2020 - AUG 2020

Upper Secondary School - Sustainable Technology

BROMANGYMANSIET, HUDIKSVALL AUG 2014 - JUN 2017

POSITIONS OF TRUST

Chapter of Media Technology, Stockholm

AUG 2018 - SEP 2021

- Project manager of the career fair Medias Branschdag
- Account manager of the career fair Medias Branschdag
- Event planner of yearly ski trip
- Event manager of Student Reception, twice
- Art director of the communications board

WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesperson

CIRCLE K, MÄRSTA AND HUDIKSVALL MAY 2017 – DEC 2017

- Retail salesperson at two different stations
- Cooked fast food for customers
- Was private chauffeur to business customers
- Managed car rental and washing services

Consultant

2COMPLETE, STOCKHOLM MAR 2019 - MAY 2019

- Seasonal work at a tire washing station
- Organized and washed tires
- Transported tires in a small truck to other stations